

Nassim El Khantour

Multimedia Designer :: Art Director :: Web Developer

I am a French creative with an expertise in Web and Motion Design, but also proficiencies in development, 3D design, and illustration. An extended skill set I put at work in various projects for the past 5 years such as music videos, web apps, as well as audiovisual interactive setups. I am now looking to settle in Taiwan.

- Montréal, Canada
- (+33) 6 35 17 69 16
- nasselkh
- nassim.elkhantour@gmail.com
- elkhantour.com
- in linkedin.com/in/nassimelkhantour
- Bē behance.net/elkhantour

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



Lead Designer: Motion, Web & Print productions

2022 - Present

Design of visual and interactive content going from websites to print and motion design assets.

- Production of motion design materials and sound design (google, meta, tiktoks ads, marketing collaterals, as well as product showcases...)
- Supervision of junior designers ensuring their work fit the established art directions.
- Design of websites and print assets.
- Branding and visual identity design.
- · Videography and photo editing of the agency's events and venues.
- Providing web developers JS libraries to improve websites user experience (3D WebGL interactive content, SVG/SCSS/GSAP animations...)
- Setup and development of web apps and Adobe extensions to enhance the agency workflow.

Redbox Media Inc. :: Montréal, Canada



Web Designer & Developer

2020 - 2022

- Development and UX/UI design of LAOS: a web browser extension to improve Mandarin learning.
- Development and Web Design of an e-commerce coupled with a SQL client for products management.
- Development and UX/UI design of KINOJI: a website archiving various cinematographic content (MERN stack).
- Art direction, background painting and animation for an animated short-movie (music video).

Freelance:: Strasbourg, France

NEK Graphic & Multimedia designer

2016 - 2020

Providing visuals for various cultural structures such as associations, music acts and soundsystems.

- Spatial organisation and scenography of various video-mapping installations.
- Art direction and animation for an animated short-movie (music video).
- 3D modelling, animation and compositing of more than a 100 visual samples made to be projected during events.
- Development and UI design of interactive audiovisual software (motion design, generative art).

Independent contractor :: Nancy, France

EDUCATION

DNSEP with summa cum laude

2019 - 2020

Master's degree in Digital Art.

ENSAD (École Nationale Supérieure d'Art et de Design) Nancy, France



Web/Game Design, Illustration & **3D Animation**

2018 - 2019

International exchange program.

IUP (Indiana University of Pennsylvania) Indiana (PA), USA

DNA with honors

2015 - 2018

Bachelor's degree (National Diploma of Art) in Digital Art. ENSAD (École Nationale Supérieure d'Art et de Design) Nancy, France

LANGUAGES

French (native)

English (fluent)

Mandarin (intermediate)

German (basic)

TECHNICALS

Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro, Figma, XD, After Effects, InDesign, Audition, Logic Pro X

HTML, CSS, JS, Python, SQL (basic), PHP, C# (basic)

Maya, ZBrush, Blender, Substance Painter, Unity

TouchDesigner, Resolume Arena, MaxMSP

AWARDS

Winner of Vibrations Urbaines Music Video Festival

For Philip Pentacle - Animal Chamber Apocalypse Beat (ACAB)

2022 :: Le Grillen, Ville de Colmar

1/2 English

COMMUNITY SERVICE

mm Montrez-moi vos muscles Record

Member and Visual Artist at Montrez-moi vos muscles music record (VJ, music video).

2019 - Present :: Strasbourg, France

WIUP radio station

Member of the Music Team, selecting musics and helping the Web Team.

2018 - 2019 :: Indiana (PA), USA

HUMMUß GAFFER

Experiential art research with Clémence Fontaine.

2016 - 2018 :: Nancy, France

ENSAD BDE (students office)

Communication manager, designing events' communication media (posters, social media ads...)

2016 - 2017 :: Nancy, France

PRESS & CURATED WORK

PHILIP PENTACLE – ANIMAL CHAMBER APOCALYPSE BEAT [OCTOBER TONE]

2021:: Fedelab.fr

Un nouveau clip très animé pour Philip Pentacle

April 19th, 2021 :: Lalsace.fr

[NOUVEAUTÉ] PHILIP PENTACLE – ANIMAL CHAMBER APOCALYPSE BEAT

March 3rd, 2021:: Mesenceintesfontdefaut.com

Les clips de la semaine #39

December 14th, 2020 :: Phenixwebtv.com

PERFORMANCES & EXHIBITIONS (SELECTION)

Maison Mimir fête ses 10 ans, with Philip Pentacle and Epic Schmetterling.

March 3rd, 2020 :: MOLODOÏ, Strasbourg, France

ART'ung Live, with Philip pentacle, Noyus and Epic Schmetterling.

February 15th, 2020 :: Local ART'ung, Willerhoff, France

CELEBRATION, with Epic Schmetterling.

December 5th, 2019 :: ENSAD, Nancy, France

 $\begin{tabular}{ll} \textbf{Limedia Party #1}, as part of the RING festival, with CTL! \\ soundsystem. \end{tabular}$

April 14th, 2018 :: Théatre de la Manufacture, Nancy, France

TECHNO, with ENSAD (BDE).

February 22nd, 2018 :: LNVRS club, Nancy, France

CTL PARTY!, with CTL! soundsystem.

November 4th, 2017 :: Ostra club, Nancy, France

Ph pas neutre: Jaquarius, with CTL! soundsystem.

October 6th, 2017:: LNVRS club, Nancy, France

Festival Moumouth Fest, with Epic Schmetterling.

May 7th, 2017 :: Tanneries, Dijon, France

ARK4-Artem, with Latitudes 5.4.

January 19th, 2017:: CCAM, Vandoeuvre-les-Nancy, France

Freshmen homecoming, with ENSAD (BDE).

December 8th, 2016 :: Appart club, Nancy, France

RELATED SKILLS

Illustration • Visual development • Web design • Concept art • Motion graphic • Photography • Video compositing • Video editing • Sound design

English 2/2